# IRWIN KAMUJUBA ZGAMBO

Recent M.Sc. graduate from Kazan National Research and Technological University - Russia





#### **SUMMARY**

Recent M.Sc. graduate from Kazan National Research and Technological University – Russia. Has research background in automated process control system. Experience working in an IT Company as an Engineer with focus on cyber security and also experience as a freelancer in web development and administration

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Dispatcher/Logistic**

STI Trucking USA, New York(Remote). May 2022 - To date

- Organizing drivers Eld's and routes -Looking into the safety of the trucks and drivers of over 120 drivers
- Creating weekly reports about fleet servicing
- Monitoring the driver routes, to avoid usage of toll roads, unsafe roads and long routes using samsara,
- help with on road truck and reefer service
- built a fleet management system for the company using postgres express is React and typescript

#### Junior wordpress web developer

SmartData Russia, Kazan. October 2021 – December 2021

- Write websites in wordpress and also optimize websites made in wordpress.

#### Freelancer 2019 - 2020

- Writing websites from scratch using php, javascript, Mysql and html.



GDC (Fujitsu) Russia, Kazan. June 2019 - August 2019.

- Cyber security
  - Built and configured windows servers and clients on Vmware.
  - Worked on installation of an antivirus Mcafee epo on the windows server, deploying agents on windows clients and linux. configured policies to the Epo and agents
    - Worked on installation of an antivirus Trend Micro Deep Security on the windows server, deploying agents on windows clients and linux. configured policies on Trend Micro and agents
  - Configured elastic search on windows server and clients machines, to be able to get logs.
  - Worked on installation of an antivirus Norton on the windows server, installing agents on windows clients and linux. configured policies on the server and agents
  - Worked with packet tracer, configured routers, switchers, computers, made vlans and networks.

# **Intern Website Development**

- Kazan National Research Technological University - faculty of Control and Automation. April 2017 - June 2017 • Designing and programing a dynamic website for foreigners in the city using



# **Intern Website Development**

- Procharter Zambia . *February 2018 september 2018* 
  - Designing and programing a dynamic website for the company using Php, Html, Css, Mysql and Javascript.

# **PROJECTS**

- Ecommerce web portal
 This is intended to be used in

 Zambia. https://www.zglobalmarket.com/

- *Inter-city travelling app*.

The project is in the planning phase.

#### **EDUCATION**

M.Sc. with Honors in Informatics and Computer Engineering.

Kazan National Research Technological University.

2018 – 2020 Kazan, Russia.

Thesis: "Development of a Catalytic Reforming Model in the Omegaland Environment (Yokagawa)"

- Russian Government scholarship recipient

# Bachelor's Degree with Honors in Informatics and Computer Engineering.

Kazan National Research Technological University.

2013 – 2017 **♀** Kazan, Russia.

Thesis: "Design of Information Portal of International Students Assistance"

- Russian Government scholarship recipient

# **SKILLS**

- ➤ Knowledge in Mcafee EPO, Norton and Trend Micro Deep Security
  - ➤ Knowledge in programming languages Php, Javascript, Mysql, and I am learning Kotlin
  - ➤ Knowledgeable in windows administration
  - ➤ Packet tracer, Git, LAN & WAN Config

# PUBLIC SERVICE/ VOLUNTEER Vice President-

#### **Sports**

Association of International Students and Post-graduates.

2014-2016 Lazan, Russia - Led a multicultural team of students from different Countries.

 Organized sports event for students - Created a fanbase for students

## **Vice President**

Association of African Students in Kazan.

2015 -2016 Kazan, Russia - Led a group of students from African countries, helped with adaptation and organized events.

- Launched several projects.

#### **President**

Association of Zambian Students in Kazan

2015 - 2016 Kazan, Russia - Led a group of students from Zambia, helped with adaptation and organized events so as to make them feel at home.

# **LANGUAGES**

- Nyanja (Zambian Language) -

- Russian

# REFERENCES

Prof. Dr. Rustem N. Gainullin

Email: gainullin@kstu.ru

Tel: +78432314359

Website: www.kstu.ru

Chair; Department of

Automated Data Acquisition

and Processing Systems

Institute of Automated Control

Systems and Information

Technologies Kazan National

Research Technological

University.

Docent Maria M. Volkova

Kazan National Research Technological

University

Department of Automated Systems of

Information Collection and Processing

Email: m.volkova@abiroy.com

Tel: +79046610162

Master's thesis Supervisor

Docent Staroverova Natalia Aleksandrovna

Kazan National Research Technological

University

Department of Automated Systems of

**Information Collection and Processing** 

Email: nata-staroverova@yandex.ru

Engineer Samuel Sichamba

Procharter Zambia

Aircraft Maintenance Planner/IT support

Email:sam.sichamba@procharterzambia.com

Tel:+260 97 2436580.

Tumbuka (Zambian Language) -Bemba (Zambian Language)

- English